

About Me

Innovative thinker who's constantly pushing myself to reach higher heights. With over 5 years of programming experience and over 10 years of experience of graphic design, I would consider myself a hybrid in today's job market. With contract and professional experience I know the importance of project management and overall customer satisfaction.

Contact



j@qmoneyenterprise.com



405.924.2744



Jerrod Crawford

Skills

HTML Adobe Illustrator
CSS Attention to Detail
Javascript Effective Listening
PHP Critical Thinking
Adobe Photoshop Project Management

References

Derrick Mitchell 405.534.0304
Tremaine Truitt 405.255.8811
Henry Newby 405.412.6355

Work Experience

Web Master/Graphic Designer Pictur-It Designs

05/2011 - 11/2018

- Decianed and n
- Designed and maintained company's website.
- Created print ready t-shirt designs.

Graphic Designer Paradigm AdvantEdge

04/2012 - 04/2013

- Created branding material for Realtors and associates.
- Designed and maintained company's website.

Digital Imaging Tech Reflective Edge

04/2007 - 04/2012

- Assisted customers with creating artwork.
- Managed print inventory.
- Designed and maintained company's website.

Education

AAS in Graphic Communications 2010
Oklahoma City Community College